Let's give us your reaction on what went
on today. Yeah.
No, no, no it's not. Don't usually get
to say that, but no, it was a lot of
fun, man. It was so fun being out here
back with the guys. Like a lot of us,
man, I haven't seen a lot of those guys
since, you know, I went went back to
California to train, and it's good to be
back and see those guys and be able to
throw those guys. It it was so fun to
see them. I mean, DG's looking cut up,
Scoozy looked really good today. A lot
of those guys balled out today. Casey's
running fast, and so it was a lot of fun
to be out there
throwing with the guys, be out there
with the guys again. It was good vibes,
good energy in there. What are some of
the most I'm sorry. What are some of the
most important things maybe you learned
today by being around the scouts and
these NFL coaches?
Uh I mean, honestly, it's just about
going out and do what you can and just
kind of let go. That's the biggest thing
is just be able to go out there and just
sling it and do your thing and let
everything else take care of itself.
That's kind of been my thing, and you
know, I feel like I got to get a rapport
with the scouts and stuff like that, and
so it's been fun process navigating
everything and
just getting in there and doing my
thing. Is there any particular thing
that maybe the advice they gave you,
some good advice that they said, "Hey,
maybe try to work on this little bit
more." or something kind of soaked in a
little bit from them?
>> Yeah, I mean, uh like they I I ask guys
and, you know, some scouts out there,
and they just like, "Man, just keep
working your tail off. Get Whenever you
get in the building, be the first guy
in, last guy out. Be a grinder. Be Be a
guy who shows up. Obviously a team guy.
Be a leader and do your thing." And
like, you you know, they just tell me
that like my position is go out there
and give them every reason to keep
putting you on the roster and never cut
you. So
It's all good.
Wait on it. You
You praised the other guys, but I mean,
how do you feel like how would you
evaluate how your performance was today?
Yeah, I feel like I threw the ball
really well. I think it was jumping off
my hand. It was good to be back. You
know, we practiced a a decent amount
last year in this indoor facility
during, you know, weather or fall camp
when it was too hot to stand outside or
whatever it was. And uh we had fun. And
so like coming back in here throwing
with those guys, the lighting is kind of
weird for the receivers, so we had to
get a little warmed up there. We had a
couple weird ones, but other than that,
like it it's awesome throwing in there.
I feel like I threw the ball really well
today. I feel like, you know, I've been
training for the last what, 3 months
now, and I feel like it's paid off in a
lot of great ways today. You threw here
today. How much did you do at BYU? Same
thing. All I did was throw. Have you met
with any NFL teams outside of this
already? Yeah, yeah, I talked to a
a handful of teams, and you know, at the
Hula Bowl, I got to talk to pretty much
every scout that was there, and more
than half the league I had conversations
with, and you know, getting closer and
closer. I'm excited for you know, the
local day here with the Saints on
Friday.
You know, just talking to the
quarterback coach here, and so
it's just like, you know, it's here and
there, and it's Zoom calls here and
there, and talking to a bunch of scouts,
and you know, obviously this month is
going to be a a fun month to just kind
of you know, not sit and wait around,
but basically sit and wait around, stay
in shape, stay working out. Obviously
take every opportunity I got to get in
front of the the guy the the coaches and
the scouts and get good looks. You have
such a unique situation where you showed
up here what, like 30 days before the
season or something like that, and then
you end up not just, you know, starting
and earning the job, but helping lead
this team to the college football
playoff. Did Did that experience come up
in those meetings? Do you think that's
something that can help give you a leg
up, the fact that you were able to
adjust so quickly on the fly? Yeah, I I
think that if there was ever a question
about my adaptability or, you know, my
ability to learn an offense, that's
that's answered pretty quickly by just
my story coming here to Tulane so late.
And so
that's definitely not a question I worry
about. And it's And it's good that that
guys people have that in the back of
their minds where they, you know, Tulane
went to the college football playoff for
the first time program history this
year. And like that was a huge deal, and
so they're giving us points for that.
And obviously that's not me, that's this
whole team here and all these seniors
here doing that. So
yeah, I mean, that's giving us some
brownie points here and there, but you
know,
it's a good deal. It's definitely fun.
Where do you think you'll be for the
draft? Are you
Where are you going to watch it? Yeah,
I'll probably be with my family
somewhere around a TV back home in
California most likely.
I'm just excited to spend that time with
them. My brother's going through the
same thing right now, and so we're
excited for him to get a call to get to
get to a camp invite. And then whatever
happens happens, and yeah, it'll be a
family deal. We'll just keep it nice and
private. How optimistic are you about
the draft and your situation?
>> Yeah, I mean, I'm optimistic to get now.
I know I'm going to get opportunities.
It's a matter of when and where. And
I mean, as you could tell from what we
talked about, my story getting here late
and all that stuff, I'm just care about
just tell me where to be and when. Like
let me I'll handle the rest from there.
Everything now in between there, it's a
lot of it's out of my control. Some of
it is when I can do interviews and
meetings with scouts and and coaches,
and so uh
you know, just like I said, tell me what
where to be and when, and and I'll show
up and put my best foot forward.